hey guys welcome to this limit problem
so as you know as X approaches 3 we
ultimately can just plug in a 3 for the
X and what happens when we do that is we
get 3 - 3 over 3^ 2 - 9 and this ends up
giving us 0 over 0 so anytime you have a
0 over 0 you should look to see if
something can cancel after you factor so
this is actually difference of two
squared so I'm going to rewrite this as
the limit is X approaches
3 of x - 3 over and I'm going to factor
this x -
3 x +
3 and now these two things can cancel
and we're left with just a one on top
now when I plug in the three for the X I
end up with 1 over 3 +
3 which is equal to to 1
6 and that is the answer to the question
so I hope that makes sense and I'll talk
to you guys soon
bye